LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate the face of light
Save your tears for the day
when our pain is far behind
on your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
Saturday
Night
and
Sunday
Morning
Ah, thank you for coming, Aramaki-kun.
I don't believe we had a choice.
The one who badgered the Prime Minister into
ordering us to come was you, Chairman Tadokoro.
Now, now, don't be so angry.
Ever since that theft of
electronic funds occurred,
I've become unwilling to trust security
companies and the Prefectural Police.
Let us go to the heart of the
matter and hear your concerns.
Well... Actually, that hacker...
Hmm, what was her name...
If I recall correctly, it was...
Cash Eye, was it?
Ah, yes. She delivered this warning yesterday.
After that robbery,
I decided to convert my assets to cash.
So, my entire fortune is currently stored
in this building's underground safe.
I see.
In a sense, that might be the best
security you can provide for your wealth.
I thought so myself, but last night, the hacker
took remote control of a female house android.
Take a look.
Even though she was easily able to
infiltrate the building and come to this room,
she then deliberately destroyed the security
camera to alert security about the breach,
and made her escape by leaping from this
window, fifty floors above ground.
This would seem to be a message to us that
physically preventing the robbery is impossible.
It seems that way.
Judging from what you've told us,
this does not seem to fall
within Section 9's jurisdiction.
Considering their superior numbers, I believe it
would be wiser to notify the Prefectural Police,
rather than to ask Section 9,
which is a small, elite group.
Unfortunately, it's not that simple.
Tomorrow night,
when the theft is supposed to take place,
there will be a certain secret party here attended
by several political and business heavyweights.
Of course, it's nothing illegal;
it's just a private party for those
of us who share similar "tastes".
However, it's not an event where we
can tolerate any uncultured visitors.
In addition, we can neither
relocate nor delay the event.
I'm sure you understand.
Important policies are sometimes
formulated at such events.
This is why I need help from a
source that is capable of discretion.
I will use the security company
personnel to boost security.
My most pressing need is to have someone
capable of supervising the entire operation.
It appears we cannot refuse, considering
that the order has to come from the top.
What are you saying?
I now know why the Prime Minister recommended you.
I can almost smell her white blood.
She is not an android.
Oh, my apologies,
but the inorganic qualities of a multi-purpose, fully cybernetic
body arouse my libido in the same way as an android does.
She must really despise him. Prime Minister Kayabuki, I mean.
Regardless of your personal
impressions regarding this affair,
you must understand that she is taking this course of action
to push through reforms that have been meeting resistance.
Considering that she also seeks to eliminate the
previous regime's lingering traces, it is a just move.
A woman's grudge; how terrifying.
I'm not happy about being made
an accomplice to her revenge,
not to mention the fact that I don't think it's a job
worth being made to give up our vacation for.
I'm sorry.
A whole pile of even more infuriating things
await tomorrow, so don't lose your temper now.
Can you see?
Sure can.
Hey, that guy who just arrived is an
executive at Hanka Precision Instruments.
To think that political and business power brokers are attending
a party behind their wives' backs to show off their "dutch" wives...
How sad.
Oh, check this out.
We have the former Minister of Foreign Affairs.
He'll never learn his lesson.
Damn.
How depressing.
Hey, the Chief and Major have arrived.
This'll be interesting...
How depressing.
Whoa, don't you think the old man's a
bit more enthusiastic than planned?
Agreed.
But anyway, look at the Major; she's
an instant hit with those freaks.
Holy shit! Someone touched her butt!
Ignorance is bliss, I guess?
All right, let's leave the passport into the
underground safe to the Major,
and get started with our own business.
Check.
Let's head towards the party.
Tachikoma, are you ready?
All done!
We're all done over here, too!
All right, wait for the Major's signal.
You have made a wise decision, Aramaki-kun.
Your camouflage is exceptional.
My subordinates are already in position;
discreetly, so as not to disturb the party.
Well, consider our security measures.
Even supposing that the
thief makes it into the safe,
I find it hard to believe that she'll
be able to carry out all the cash.
Her track record speaks for itself, though,
so catch her at any cost.
I understand.
Until the time the theft will supposedly
occur, we should all join the party.
How about it?
Would you like a short tour of my home?
It would be my pleasure.
Ishikawa, status report.
It doesn't look too good.
It now appears probable that Tadokoro's underground safe
was reinforced with additional security devices a few days ago.
I've hacked the device maker's server,
but the blueprints of all the newly installed
components have already been deleted.
Their information security is very tight.
The hard copy of the blueprints
is probably lost as well.
The Major has gone to retrieve Tadokoro's
retinal and cyberbrain patterns.
Even if she succeeds in obtaining them,
her efforts won't matter if the
safe itself can't be opened.
I'll find another way to open it, somehow.
Hurry.
You may scoff at our outlandish tastes,
but after our exhaustive experience
with so many various pleasures,
we have come to find doll fetishism satisfying.
What do you think?
Every one of these dolls was custom made
by a famous designer, from constituent parts.
They're "haute couture".
Their bodies' functions are
not so different from yours.
Would you happen to be interested
in trying on any of their bodies?
Major, how is it going?
This really is sexual harassment.
Oh, sorry about that.
I can't help but indulge my habits.
Still, that body of yours...
At first glance, it's just multi-purpose,
but it's actually very elaborately
made, down to the last detail.
Let me guess; your skin's sensory
receptor count must be 16 squared.
Bear with it for now.
I know, but I wouldn't be
able to stomach his touch,
so I've cut off input from my sensory organs.
I see.
So, how about a try?
Begin the operation now.
I understand.
Could it be that you want to make
love to my body while I am "absent"?
You seem to understand my tastes very well.
Wouldn't it be better to be able to treat a conscious
human being as if she were a doll, instead?
I'll leave my sensory input on,
and won't make a single move...
Sorry about that, but I don't want to risk letting
you continue and giving you a heart attack, either.
So, enjoy the rest in your dreams...
Chief, I've got the retinal
and cyberbrain patterns.
All right, let's proceed to stage two.
Roger that.
Batou, Togusa, how are things on your end?
We're just about to start now.
Ishikawa.
Leave it to me.
Hey, this place is off limits...
We've been sent by Tadokoro-San.
Security camera monitor footage switch complete.
Good job, Tachikoma.
Of course!
Stop right there!
Good. Now, we just have to wait
for the Major to get here...
I'm already here.
Were you able to get the info?
Of course.
You might just as well have infiltrated
Tadokoro's cyberbrain and brought him here.
I couldn't quite do that.
There's still something we need to have him do.
Can't we disable that system?
It's an isolated system.
If you destroy it, the control centre will
immediately notice that something's wrong.
The system isn't a serious problem.
It's whether or not I can open the safe.
I managed to work something out.
I've assessed the safe's structure, based on the scale
of the materials brought into the Tadokoro Building.
They've deliberately chosen an analog safe with a locking
mechanism that features four layers of antiquated locks.
Wouldn't it be better to just bring Tadokoro here?
We can't do that now.
Ishikawa, how about going with Code B?
Yeah, should be a go.
The explosives we have prepared should be more
than enough to burn through the safe's supports.
However, our operation will become
known at that point in time.
That's unavoidable.
There's another problem.
Even if you manage to break into the safe,
We don't know what traps may be inside.
There may be a double barrier, for all we know.
"Nothing ventured, nothing gained."
Since it's not our intention to steal
cash, I couldn't care less.
All right; let's go with Code B.
The rest of us can't get any
closer to the safe, though.
Be careful.
Thank you for your concern.
Time to move.
We'll have to get going ourselves
to prep for the next stage.
So this is where you were.
Aramaki-kun...
It's already this late?
How is the party going?
No interruptions of any kind.
It is almost the time when the
theft is supposed to occur.
Ah, yes...
I hope nothing happens, but...
Chief, please hurry to the control room.
It appears that we have an intruder.
What?!
I wonder if it's almost time...
Tachikoma!
Are you ready?
I've been waiting for your signal!
I'm ready to go anytime!
I believe the building has switched
over to its internal power generator.
Let's hurry.
Everyone, there is nothing to worry about!
However, considering the nature of this
party, we must avoid any accidents.
Please follow our instructions and
evacuate the hall as quickly as possible.
Please take a look at this.
This is the one that came here yesterday!
How did the hacker get all the way in there?!
I will send my team there right away.
No, wait.
The hacker apparently intends to break into
the safe, but either way she'll be cornered.
What exactly do you mean by that?
When someone other than myself enters that safe,
double security doors will close,
and they will not open again
without my "ghost" generated key.
A "ghost" generated key...
More importantly, find the hacker who
is remotely controlling that android!
That person's the one you should capture!
Chief!
It appears that the figure we see on the
monitors is either a completely independent AI
or a full body cyborg. There is no evidence that
a remote control signal is being transmitted.
Then this is the hacker herself?
Yes.
In addition, we just received another warning.
Aramaki-kun! Come with me to the safe
and confirm that the hacker's
death is legitimate self-defence.
The safe will be sealed off, and a near-vacuum
state will persist for a length of time.
Even if the hacker's a full body cyborg,
there's no way she can survive that!
What are you waiting for?!
Chief... what about the Major?
Well, how is it?
Did you find the body?!
It does not seem to be here.
How can that be?
Look closer!
I'm sorry to have kept everyone waiting.
It's just that Chairman
Tadokoro was so impressive...
Oh, uh...
Major, how did you...
The footage you saw of me going inside was
artificial imagery I had Tachikoma make.
Ta-dah!
By the way, Chairman Tadokoro...
Yes?
Is it safe to assume that these
piles of currency are all yours,
judging from the fact that they are in this safe?
Of course.
What are you saying?
Investigate.
What are you doing?!
Look for the thief's body!
Chairman Tadokoro, our true motive was
to make you open the safe yourself,
so we could inspect the serial
numbers of the bills within the safe.
We have obtained information that you are managing the rest
of former Secretary General Yakushima's hidden assets,
so we conducted a secret investigation.
Major?
The serial numbers correspond with
those given to us by the Tax Bureau
I doubt you can account for this legally.
We have quite a few questions for you,
so please come to headquarters with us.
We came
in to conduct an inspection
Tax Bureau Inspections Division
Please hurry!
How are things going over there?
We're letting them go as planned.
After all, there's a good possibility that more hidden
gold will come rolling out if we follow these leads.
Are those people perverts?
Or rather, hobbyists, maybe?
Tadokoro Tsutomu,
the former Chairman of Keidanren,
who is also said to have strong political ties,
was arrested for suspected massive tax
evasion and laundering of slush funds.
Playing a thief was pretty fun, wasn't it?
Still, I was worried for a second there.
I thought you might become a vacuum-packed Major.
You know, it's called "teamwork" when you let
your team members know your plan beforehand.
Oh? Thievery is a profession that
includes deception as an ironclad rule.
How long do you intend to
fantasise about being a thief?
There's a lot of work to do!
Maybe I should consider a new career...
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
and singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(Our time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside, (the time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.